{
    "id": "75cfe71cda2448c2aa8c34357aacff9d",
    "title": "Prepositions Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The child ran ..................... the road.",
            "description": "Across means 'on or to the other side of a flat area or surface. ",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "through",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "687e20048c5f44e4aa23fa09a5a40724"
        },
        {
            "question": "The river flows ..................... the bridge.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "under",
                "below",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3507b106c9174f71b58516d229528992"
        },
        {
            "question": "The work was done ………………….. haste.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b34681fbd6ee46e2a80230c67a130c97"
        },
        {
            "question": "He goes ..................... church every Sunday.",
            "description": "To indicates direction.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "in",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "580a8b9121594961816c756fe3ee74e3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The thieves jumped ..................... the wall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "above",
                "over",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6ac74bcec5da406099628eb99f913e16"
        },
        {
            "question": "He spoke ..................... me ………………… French.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for, in",
                "to, in",
                "to, with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a4861514db434ea88d7e03a25d108ac0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The moon does not shine ...................... its own light.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1da9adf5f0f5424f87a7cdacfa8ae5c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am tired ………………… walking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "of",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d80745389565460499af0776e98a717e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has yet to recover ..................... his illness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a4ac7f48ffc149a4ad3168b692055aa4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do not cry …………………. spilt milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f46529ba0d4c4fda80b7acf7225d87ea"
        }
    ]
}